<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yaya Guo&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://yayaguo.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yaya Guo&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://yayaguo.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/cheat_sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/cheat_sheet/</guid>
      
        <description>Markdown Cheat Sheet Thanks for visiting The Markdown Guide!
This Markdown cheat sheet provides a quick overview of all the Markdown syntax elements. It can’t cover every edge case, so if you need more information about any of these elements, refer to the reference guides for basic syntax and extended syntax.
Basic Syntax These are the elements outlined in John Gruber’s original design document. All Markdown applications support these elements.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/index_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/index_backup/</guid>
      
        <description>Yanan (Yaya) Guo Hi there! I am currently a third-year PhD student at the University of Pittsburgh, working with my advisor Dr. Jun Yang in the Electrical and Computer Engineering Department. I graduated from Xidian University in 2018 with a B.S. in whatever.
My research interest lies in the areas of computer architecture and security, with a focus on memory attacks and defenses, ML attacks and defenses, and quantum computer.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/publication/</guid>
      
        <description>[C]Yanan Guo, Christopher Dipalma, Takami Sato, Yulong Cal, Alfred Chen, Yueqiang Cheng, An Adversarial Attack on DNN-based Adaptive Cruise Control Systems. (ICCV&#39;21 Workshop).  
[C]Yanan Guo, Andrew Zigerelli, Youtao Zhang, Jun Yang, Performance-Enhanced Integrity Verification for Large Memories. In Proceedings of the 1st IEEE International Symposium on Secure and Private Execution Environment Design (SEED&#39;21). 
[C] Xin Xin, Yanan Guo, Youtao Zhang, Jun Yang, SAM: Accelerating Strided Memory Accesses. In Proceedings of the 54th IEEE/ACM International Symposium on Microarchitecture (MICRO&#39;21).</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>