<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yanan Guo&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://yananguo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yanan Guo&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://yananguo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/cheat_sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/cheat_sheet/</guid>
      
        <description>Markdown Cheat Sheet Thanks for visiting The Markdown Guide!
This Markdown cheat sheet provides a quick overview of all the Markdown syntax elements. It can’t cover every edge case, so if you need more information about any of these elements, refer to the reference guides for basic syntax and extended syntax.
Basic Syntax These are the elements outlined in John Gruber’s original design document. All Markdown applications support these elements.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/lucky/</guid>
      
        <description>Here is Lucky Guo </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/publications/</guid>
      
        <description>[Sorted by time] [Sorted by topic] [Under submission] Invalidate+Compare: A Timer-Free GPU Cache Attack Primitive
Zhenkai Zhang, Kunbei Cai, Yanan Guo, Fan Yao, and Xing Gao
33rd USENIX Security Symposium.
(USENIX Security&#39;24)
Uncore Encore: Covert Channels Exploiting Uncore Frequency Scaling
Yanan Guo, Dingyuan Cao, Xin Xin, Youtao Zhang, and Jun Yang
56th IEEE/ACM International Symposium on Microarchitecture.
(MICRO&#39;23)
IDYLL: Enhancing Page Translation in Multi-GPUs via Light Weight PTE Invalidations Bingyao Li, Yanan Guo, Yueqi Wang, Aamer Jaleel, Jun Yang, and Xulong Tang</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/publications_field/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/publications_field/</guid>
      
        <description>[Sorted by time] [Sorted by topic] [Under submission] Microarchitectural Side Channels:
Uncore Encore: Covert Channels Exploiting Uncore Frequency Scaling
Yanan Guo, Dingyuan Cao, Xin Xin, Youtao Zhang, and Jun Yang
56th IEEE/ACM International Symposium on Microarchitecture.
(MICRO&#39;23)
Leaky Way: A Conflict-Based Cache Covert Channel Bypassing Set Associativity
Yanan Guo, Xin Xin, Youtao Zhang, Jun Yang
55th IEEE/ACM International Symposium on Microarchitecture.
(MICRO&#39;22)
Adversarial Prefetch: New Cross-Core Cache Side Channel Attacks</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/research/</guid>
      
        <description>12/2022 Cache Side Channel Attacks on Modern Processors. At the Southeast University. 10/2022 Leaky Way: A Conflict-Based Cache Covert Channel Bypassing Set Associativity. At MICRO&#39;22. 06/2022 Adversarial Prefetch: New Cross-Core Cache Side Channel Attacks. At Nvidia. 05/2022 Adversarial Prefetch: New Cross-Core Cache Side Channel Attacks. At Oakland&#39;22. 02/2022 Q-GPU: A Recipe of Optimizations for Quantum Circuit Simulation Using GPUs. At HPCA&#39;22. 10/2021 ModelShield: A Generic and Portable Framework Extension for Defending Bit-Flip based Adversarial Weight Attacks.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/submission/</guid>
      
        <description>[Sorted by time] [Sorted by topic] [Under submission] GPU Memory Exploitation for Fun and Profit
Yanan Guo, Zhenkai Zhang, and Jun Yang
Under submission.
Developted multiple GPU memory corruption attacks, including the first GPU return-oriented programming attack.
Invalidate+Compare: A Timer-Free GPU Cache Attack Primitive
Zhenkai Zhang, Kunbei Cai, Yanan Guo, Fan Yao, Xing Gao
Under submission.
Developed the first timer-free GPU cache side-channel attack.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yananguo.com/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yananguo.com/talks/</guid>
      
        <description>Leaky Hardware: Side Channel Attacks on Modern Processors
-ByteDance
Adversarial Prefetch: New Cross-Core Cache Side Channel Attacks
-Top Picks in Hardware and Embedded Security 2023
-Nvidia
-Oakland&#39;22
Cache Side Channel Attacks on Modern Processors
-Southeast University
-University of Pittsburgh
Leaky Way: A Conflict-Based Cache Covert Channel Bypassing Set Associativity
-MICRO&#39;22
Adversarial Attacks on DNN-based Adaptive Cruise Control Systems
-SafeThings&#39;23
-NIO
Prefetch-Based Cache Side Channel Attacks
-CWIDCA&#39;22
Q-GPU: A Recipe of Optimizations for Quantum Circuit Simulation Using GPUs</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>