<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yaya Guo&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://yayaguo.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Yaya Guo&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://yayaguo.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/cheat_sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/cheat_sheet/</guid>
      
        <description>Markdown Cheat Sheet Thanks for visiting The Markdown Guide!
This Markdown cheat sheet provides a quick overview of all the Markdown syntax elements. It can’t cover every edge case, so if you need more information about any of these elements, refer to the reference guides for basic syntax and extended syntax.
Basic Syntax These are the elements outlined in John Gruber’s original design document. All Markdown applications support these elements.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/index_backup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/index_backup/</guid>
      
        <description>Yanan (Yaya) Guo Hi there! I am currently a third-year PhD student at the University of Pittsburgh, working with my advisor Dr. Jun Yang in the Electrical and Computer Engineering Department. I graduated from Xidian University in 2018 with a B.S. in whatever.
My research interest lies in the areas of computer architecture and security, with a focus on memory attacks and defenses, ML attacks and defenses, and quantum computer.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/lucky/</guid>
      
        <description>Here is Lucky Guo </description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/publication/</guid>
      
        <description>[C] Yanan Guo, Liang Liu, Yueqiang Cheng, Youtao Zhang, and Jun Yang, ModelShield: A Generic and Portable Framework Extension for Defending Bit-Flip based Adversarial Weight Attacks. In Proceedings of the 39th IEEE International Conference on Computer Design (ICCD&#39;21). [C] Yanan Guo, Christopher Dipalma, Takami Sato, Yulong Cal, Alfred Chen, and Yueqiang Cheng, An Adversarial Attack on DNN-based Adaptive Cruise Control Systems. (ICCV&#39;21 Workshop). [C] Yanan Guo, Andrew Zigerelli, Yueqiang Cheng, Youtao Zhang, and Jun Yang, Performance-Enhanced Integrity Verification for Large Memories.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/publications/</guid>
      
        <description>[C] Yanan Guo, Xin Xin, Youtao Zhang, Jun Yang, Leaky Way: A Conflict-Based Cache Covert Channel Bypassing Set Associativity. In Proceedings of the 55th IEEE/ACM International Symposium on Microarchitecture (MICRO&#39;22). (MICRO&#39;22)
[C] Yanan Guo, Andrew Zigerelli, Youtao Zhang, Jun Yang, Adversarial Prefetch: New Cross-Core Cache Side Channel Attacks. In 2022 IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy (S&amp;amp;P&#39;22). [C] Yilun Zhao, Yanan Guo, Yuan Yao, Amanda Dumi, Devin M Mulvey, Shiv Upadhyay, Youtao Zhang, Kenneth D Jordan, Jun Yang, Xulong Tang, Q-GPU: A Recipe of Optimizations for Quantum Circuit Simulation Using GPUs.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://yayaguo.net/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yayaguo.net/research/</guid>
      
        <description> </description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>